From painted foam pieces resembling delicious feasts to engineered weather, the magic of film relies on hidden details unknown and usually invisible to the unsuspecting viewer.
从看似美味盛宴的彩绘泡沫道具到人工操控的天气，电影的魅力依赖于那些隐藏起来不为人知的细节，这些细节深信不疑的观众也看不见。
So, let's explore some of the most fascinating behind-the-scenes tricks of the big screen.
那么，让我们来探索一些大银幕最迷人的幕后机关吧。
Screen trickery and cinematic illusions are a huge part of what brings stories to life, and set is key to this.
银幕欺骗花招和电影幻象是让故事栩栩如生的很大一部分原因，而布景是关键。
Consider period dramas like Sherlock and Peaky Blinders – both TV programmes changed modern street furniture like lampposts and signs by covering them up with facades or temporary structures.
想想《神探夏洛克》和《浴血黑帮》这样的时代剧——这两部电视剧都通过用幕墙或临时结构覆盖灯柱和指示牌等现代街道设施来改变它们。
Cobbled streets, a staple of many historical dramas, can be created using plastic or rubber floor tiles, which are lightweight and therefore quick to lay down and remove.
许多历史剧的主要部分——鹅卵石街道，可以使用塑料或橡胶地砖来制作，这些地砖重量轻，因此铺设和拆除都很快。
But sometimes it's not just part of a set that's made, but the entire thing.
但有时制作的不是布景的一部分，而是整个布景。
A team of 86 artists and model makers built an incredibly detailed miniature model of Hogwarts, the wizarding school in the Harry Potter series.
一个由86名艺术家和模型制作师组成的团队制作了一个细节极其丰富的霍格沃茨微缩模型，即《哈利·波特》系列中的魔法学校。
It was easier to create this than to build a real castle, and was especially used for sweeping shots of the castle's exterior.
制作这个模型比建造一座真正的城堡更容易，这个模型被专门用来拍摄城堡外景的广角镜头。
It's even possible to control the weather.
甚至还可以控制天气。
Filmmakers creating a rain scene generally don't use real rain, partly because you can't control it, but also because natural rain doesn't show up on camera very well.
拍摄雨景的电影制作人通常不会使用真实的雨，部分原因是你无法控制它，还因为自然雨在镜头中显示得不太好。
This is because the water droplets are too small, so rain machines that create bigger droplets are often used.
这是因为水滴太小，所以经常使用能制造更大水滴的造雨机。
Combine that with a dramatic backlight and the rain will glisten on screen.
再结合戏剧性的背光，雨就会在屏幕上闪闪发光。
This was likely a technique used in The Matrix, possibly alongside CGI, in the final fight scene between Agent Smith and Neo, which takes place in a torrential downpour.
这很可能是《黑客帝国》中使用的一种技巧，可能还与电脑特效一起用在史密斯探员和尼奥之间的最后一场打斗场景中，那场戏发生在倾盆大雨中。
So next time you're watching a movie, remember the movie magic – you can't believe everything you see!
所以下次你看电影时，记住电影魔法——你别相信你看到的一切！